navyseals.com 2013-05-17

# Privacy Policy | Navy SEALs

It is SOFREP’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

Website Visitors  
Like most website operators, SOFREP collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. SOFREP’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how SOFREP’s visitors use its website. From time to time, SOFREP may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

SOFREP also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. SOFREP only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information  
Certain visitors to SOFREP’s websites choose to interact with SOFREP in ways that require SOFREP to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that SOFREP gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. SOFREP collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with SOFREP. SOFREP does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Aggregated Statistics  
SOFREP may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites.SOFREP may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, SOFREP does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information  
SOFREP discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on SOFREP’s behalf or to provide services available at SOFREP’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using SOFREP’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. SOFREP will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, SOFREP discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when SOFREP believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of SOFREP, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a SOFREP website and have supplied your email address, SOFREP may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with SOFREP and our products. We primarily use our blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. SOFREP takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

Cookies  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. SOFREP uses cookies to help SOFREP identify and track visitors, their usage of SOFREP website, and their website access preferences. SOFREP visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using SOFREP’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of SOFREP’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Business Transfers  
If SOFREP, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that SOFREP goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of SOFREP may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Ads  
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by SOFREP and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Privacy Policy Changes  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, SOFREP may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in SOFREP’s sole discretion. SOFREP encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
